Good morning.Can I help you?
早上好，需要帮忙吗？
Yes.I've just been accepted on a course at the university and I'd like to try and arrange accommodation in the hall of residence.
是的，我刚入学，我想安排一间大学宿舍。
Yes,certainly.Please sit down.
当然，请坐。
What I'll do is fill in a form with you to find out a little more about your preferences and so forth. Thank you.
我会帮你填表，多了解一些你的喜好等等。谢谢。
So first of all,can I take your name? It's Anu Bhatt.
首先，你叫什么名字？安努·巴特。
Could you spell your name please? Yes.A-N-U...B-H-A double T.
请问你能拼一下吗？好的。A-N-U-B-H-A-T-T。
Thanks,and could I ask your date of birth? 31st March 1972.
谢谢，我能问一下你的出生日期吗？1972年3月31日。
Thank you.And where are you from? India.
谢谢。你来自哪里？-印度。
Oh right.And what will you be studying?
好的。你学的是什么？
I'm doing a course in nursing.
我学的是护理课。
Right,thank you.And how long would you want to stay in hall,do you think?
好的，谢谢。你想在大学宿舍住多久
Well,it'll take three years but I'd only like to stay in hall for two.
课程要学3年，但是我只在大学宿舍住两年。
I'd like to think about living outside for the third year.
第三年我想住外面。
Fine.And what did you have in mind for catering?
好的。关于饮食你是怎么考虑的？
Do you want to cook for yourself or have all your meals provided,that's full board?
你是想自己做饭还是想三餐全在学校吃？
Is there something in between?
有没有居中的方式？
Yes.You can just have evening meal provided,which is half board.
有。你可以只在学校吃晚饭，这是半食宿制。
That's what I'd prefer.
我更喜欢这样。
Yes,a lot of students opt for that.
是的，很多学生这么选
Now,with that in mind,do you have any special diet,anything we should know about?
现在，考虑到这一点的话，你有没有忌口，有什么是我们要了解的吗？
Yes,I don't take red meat. No red meat.
是的，我不吃牛羊肉。不吃牛羊肉。